A Guide to the Papers of William B. Spong, 1965-1974
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Legislative
  - Public Works - Rivers and Harbors - Ni River Watershed 1971 (Box 85)
  - Public Works - Rivers and Harbors - Salem Church Dam 1964-1967, 9 folders (Box 85)
  - Public Works - Rivers and Harbors - Salem Church Dam 1968-1972, n.d., 10 folders (Box 86)
  - Public Works - Rivers and Harbors - Tocks Island Dam 1969-1970 (Box 86)
  - Public Works - Rivers and Harbors - Verona Dam 1967-1972, 9 folders (Box 86)
  - Public Works - Roads 1967-1972, 13 folders (Box 87)
  - Public Works - Roads - American Association of State Highway Officials (AASHO) 1967 (Box 87)
  - Public Works - Roads - Bus Widths 1971 (Box 87)
  - Public Works - Roads - Commuter Reports 1968 (Box 87)
  - Public Works - Roads- Federal Aid Highway Act 1968-1970, 4 folders (Box 87)
  - Public Works - Roads - Federal Aid Highway Act - Mail 1968, 3 folders (Box 87)
  - Public Works - Roads - Federal Aid Highway Act - Reports 1968-1970 (Box 88)
  - Public Works - Roads - Federal Aid Highway Act - Testimony 1968, 2 folders (Box 88)
  - Public Works - Roads - Federal Highway Act - Drivers' Education, H.R. 14741 1970 (Box 88)
  - Public Works - Roads - Highway Beautification Act 1967-1968, 4 folders (Box 88)
  - Public Works - Roads - Highway Funds 1967, 2 folders (Box 88)
  - Public Works - Roads - Highway Safety 1967-1972, 4 folders (Box 88)
  - Public Works - Roads - Truck Weights 1969-1971, 4 folders (Box 88)
  - Public Works - Roads - Truck Weights S. 2658 1967-1968, 9 folders (Box 88)
  - Public Works - Rural Development 1968-1971 (Box 88)
  - Public Works - Shenandoah National Park Wilderness Proposal 1971 (Box 88)
  - Public Works - Tennessee Valley Authority S. 1637 1967 (Box 88)
  - Rules and Administration 1966-1972, 2 folders (Box 89)
  - Rules and Administration - Campaign Spending, S. 382 1970-1972, 4 folders (Box 89)
  - Rules and Administration - Disclosure Bill 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 89)
  - Rules and Administration - Election Reform 1972 (Box 89)
  - Rules and Administration - Senator Edward Kennedy 1969 (Box 89)
  - Rules and Administration - Pay Raise 1969 (Box 89)
  - Rules and Administration - Senate Rule 22 1967-1968, 1971, 2 folders (Box 89)
  - Rules and Administration - Seniority 1970-1972 (Box 89)
  - Rules and Administration - Veterans' Affairs Committee (S. Res. 13) 1968 (Box 89)
  - Veterans' Affairs 1971-1972 (Box 89)
  - Veterans' Affairs - Compensations & Pensions 1970-1972, 2 folders (Box 89)
  - Veterans' Affairs - Education 1971-1972 (Box 89)
  - Veterans' Affairs - Employment 1971 (Box 89)
  - Veterans' Affairs - Medical Schools & Hospitals 1970-1972 (Box 89)
  - Veterans' Affairs - National Cemetery Bill 1972 (Box 89)
  - Senate Special, Select & Joint Committees
    - Aging (Special Committee) 1967-1972 (Box 89)
    - Atomic Energy (Joint Committee) 1967 (Box 89)
    - Bicentennial (Joint Committee) 1971-1972 (Box 89)
    - Bicentennial - D.C. Area (Joint Committee) 1969-1971, 2 folders (Box 89)
    - Congressional Operations (Joint Committee) 1972 (Box 89)
    - Democratic Policy Committee 1970 (Box 89)
    - Economic (Joint Committee) 1967 & 1969, 1972 (Box 89)
    - Equal Educational Opportunity (Select Committee) 1970-1972, 4 folders (Box 90)
    - Equal Educational Opportunity - Rural Schools (Select Committee) 1968-1971, 3 folders (Box 90)
    - Immigration and Nationality Policy (Joint Committee) 1967 (Box 90)
    - Organization of the Congress (Joint Committee) 1966-1967 & 1970 (Box 90)
    - Printing (Joint Committee) 1968 (Box 90)
    - Reduction of Nonessential Federal Expenditures (Joint Committee) 1966-1967 (Box 90)
    - Small Business (Select Committee) 1967-1972 (Box 90)
    - Space and Astronautics (Special Committee) 1968 (Box 90)
    - Standards and Conduct (Select Committee) 1967-1972 (Box 90)
    - Standards and Conduct - Senator Thomas J. Dodd (Select Committee) 1967 (Box 90)
    - Un-American Activities (Special Committee) 1969 (Box 90)
  - Legislative Bills & Summaries kept by Spong's Office 1967-1971, 8 folders (Box 90)
- Federal Files
  - Executive Branch
    - Action - Peace Corps & VISTA 1972 (Box 91)
    - Agriculture 1966-1972, 11 folders (Box 91)
    - Agriculture - Agricultural Stabilization & Conservation Service 1967-1972, 6 folders (Box 91)
    - Agriculture - Agriculture/2000 Addresses by Secretary Orville L. Freeman 1967 (Box 91)
    - Agriculture - Appropriations Bill Loan Provisions 1971 (Box 91)
    - Agriculture - Butz Nomination for Secretary of Agriculture 1971 (Box 91)
    - Agriculture - Dairy Products 1967-1971 (Box 92)
    - Agriculture - Electric Cooperatives 1972 (Box 92)
    - Agriculture - Farmers Home Administration 1967-1972, 6 folders (Box 92)
    - Agriculture - Farmers Home Administration - Chatham Sewage System 1969 (Box 92)
    - Agriculture - Farmers Home Administration - Clintwood Water System, Dickinson County 1967-1972 (Box 92)
    - Agriculture - Farmers Home Administration - Clintwood Water System, Dickinson County (Form Letter Reply) 1967 (Box 92)
    - Agriculture - Farmers Home Administration - Coeburn, Virginia Water & Sewer Improvement 1966 (Box 92)
    - Agriculture - Farmers Home Administration - Ferrum College Water & Sewage Grant 1969-1970 (Box 92)
    - Agriculture - Farmers Home Administration - Goochland County Water & Sewage Grant 1972 (Box 92)
    - Agriculture - Farmers Home Administration - Lovettsville, Loudoun County Water & Sewage Grant 1970 (Box 92)
    - Agriculture - Farmers Home Administration - Patrick County Recreational Loan Application 1969 (Box 92)
    - Agriculture - Food Assistance Programs 1968-1970, 1972, 3 folders (Box 92)
    - Agriculture - Food Prices 1972 (Box 92)
    - Agriculture - Forest Service 1967-1972, 6 folders (Box 92)
    - Agriculture - Forest Service - Buffalo River Watershed Project 1972 (Box 92)
    - Agriculture - Forest Service - Clear-cutting 1971-1972 (Box 92)
    - Agriculture - Forest Service - Crabtree Falls 1969-1971 (Box 92)
    - Agriculture - Forest Service - Mount Rogers 1970-1972, 2 folders (Box 93)
    - Agriculture - Meat & Poultry 1967-1972 (Box 93)
    - Agriculture - Peanuts 1967-1972 (Box 93)
    - Agriculture - Peanut Disaster 1970-1972 (Box 93)
    - Agriculture - Pesticides 1968-1971, 2 folders (Box 93)
    - Agriculture - Rural Development Act of 1972 1972 (Box 93)
    - Agriculture - Rural Electrification Administration 1967-1972 (Box 93)
    - Agriculture - Rural Environmental Assistance Program (R.E.A.P.) 1971-1972 (Box 93)
    - Agriculture - Soil Conservation Service 1967-1971, 3 folders (Box 93)
    - Agriculture - Soybeans 1969-1970 (Box 93)
    - Agriculture - Tennessee Walking Horses 1971-1972 (Box 93)
    - Agriculture - Tobacco 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 93)
    - Agriculture - Virginia Farm Bureau Federation Correspondence (Robert B. Delano) 1968-1971 (Box 93)
    - American National Red Cross 1970-1972 (Box 93)
    - Appalachian Regional Commission 1967-1969, 5 folders (Box 93)
    - Appalachian Regional Commission 1970-1972, 3 folders (Box 94)
    - Appalachian Regional Commission - Hospitals & Nutrition Study 1969-1970 (Box 94)
    - Arms Control & Disarmament Agency 1970 (Box 94)
    - Atlantic-Pacific Interoceanic Canal Study Commission 1970 (Box 94)
    - Atomic Energy Commission 1967-1972, 5 folders (Box 94)
    - Atomic Energy Commission - Cannikin Test 1971, 2 folders (Box 94)
    - Atomic Energy Commission - Surry Power Plant 1971 (Box 94)
    - Bureau of the Budget 1967-1971 (Box 94)
    - Canal Zone Government 1967-1970 (Box 94)
    - Central Intelligence Agency 1967-1970 (Box 94)
    - Civil Aeronautics Board 1967-1972, 6 folders (Box 94)
    - Civil Aeronautics Board - Air Freight 1970 (Box 94)
    - Civil Aeronautics Board - Charter Flights 1970 (Box 94)
    - Civil Aeronautics Board - Greenbrier, West Virginia, Service to 1969-1970 (Box 94)
    - Civil Aeronautics Board - Helicoptor Service to Washington, D.C./Baltimore 1968-1969 (Box 94)
    - Civil Service Commission 1967-1972, 3 folders (Box 95)
    - Civil Service Commission - Administrative Appeals Procedure 1972 (Box 95)
    - Civil Service Commission - Bond Drive Coercion & Combined Federal Campaign 1971-1972 (Box 95)
    - Civil Service Commission - Classified Pay Increases 1971 (Box 95)
    - Civil Service Commission - Engineering Pay Raise 1967 (Box 95)
    - Civil Service Commission - Estate Tax Examiners 1968 (Box 95)
    - Civil Service Commission - Executive Order # 10988 1968 (Box 95)
    - Civil Service Commission - Executive Order # 11491 1970 (Box 95)
    - Civil Service Commission - Hatch Act 1967, 1971-1972 (Box 95)
    - Civil Service Commission - Health Insurance 1970-1972, 2 folders (Box 95)
    - Civil Service Commission - Job Information 1968-1972, 2 folders (Box 95)
    - Civil Service Commission - Occupational Health Nurses 1967-1968 (Box 95)
    - Civil Service Commission - Postal Service 1971-1972 (Box 95)
    - Civil Service Commission - Reclassification of Veterans' Administration Nurses 1969-1970 (Box 95)
    - Civil Service Commission - Retirement System & Reduction-in-Force 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 95)
    - Colleges 1970-1971 (Box 95)
    - Commerce 1967-1972, 4 folders (Box 95)
    - Commerce - A.S.G. Industries, Inc. 1971-1972 (Box 95)
    - Commerce - Census Bureau 1967-1972 (Box 95)
    - Commerce - Census Bureau - Complaints re Census 1970-1971 (Box 95)
    - Commerce - Census Bureau - Release of 1900 Census Records 1972 (Box 95)
    - Commerce - Economic Development Administration 1966-1972, 6 folders (Box 96)
    - Commerce - Economic Development Administration - Claypool Hill Project, Tazewell County, Virginia 1971-1972, 2 folders & 1 bound report (Box 96)
    - Commerce - Economic Development Administration - Newcastle Water & Sewer 1970 (Box 96)
    - Commerce - Economic Development Administration - Rappahannock College, Warsaw, Virginia 1971-1972 (Box 96)
    - Commerce - Economic Development Administration - Smith-Turner Wood Products 1968 (Box 96)
    - Commerce - Economic Development Administration - Tazewell County, Virginia Water & Sewer Authority 1967-1968 (Box 96)
    - Commerce - Environmental Science Services Administration 1967-1970 (Box 96)
    - Commerce - Flammable Carpet Test 1969-1971 (Box 96)
    - Commerce - Lumber Standards 1967-1970 (Box 96)
    - Commerce - Maritime Administration 1967-1972, 5 folders (Box 96)
    - Commerce - Maritime Administration - Longshoremen Strike 1969 (Box 96)
    - Commerce - Maritime Administration - St. Lawrence Seaway 1969 (Box 96)
    - Commerce - National Bureau of Standards 1970 (Box 96)
    - Commerce - National Marine Fisheries 1971 (Box 96)
    - Commerce - National Oceanic & Atmospheric Administration (Weather Bureau) 1971-1972 (Box 96)
    - Commerce - Office of State Technical Services 1970 (Box 96)
    - Commerce - Oil Import Task Force 1969-1970 (Box 96)
    - Commerce - Patent Office 1967 & 1971 (Box 96)
    - Contracts 1968-1972 (Box 97)
    - Contracts - Antec Corporation 1971-1972 (Box 97)
    - Contracts - Computer Sciences Corporation 1971-1972 (Box 97)
    - Contracts - Fort Lee Academic Building 1968-1969, 1972 (Box 97)
    - Contracts - Navy Family Housing 1971-1972 (Box 97)
    - Contracts - Ocean Electric Company 1969-1972 (Box 97)
    - Contracts - Remote Console Information Corporation 1971-1972 (Box 97)
    - Contracts - Royal Silver Manufacturing Company 1972 (Box 97)
    - Contracts - Virginia Electric Company 1972 (Box 97)
    - Defense 1967-1972, 8 folders (Box 97)
    - Defense - Academy Appointments 1967-1968 (Box 97)
    - Defense - Acquisitions & Disposal Reports 1969-1972 (Box 97)
    - Defense - Air Force 1967-1972, 3 folders (Box 97)
    - Defense - Air Force - Prime Base Engineer Emergency Force Program 1969 (Box 97)
    - Defense - Air Force - Transportation of Military Children 1970 (Box 97)
    - Defense - Anti-Ballistic Missiles 1967-1968 (Box 97)
    - Defense - Arlington Hall Property 1972 (Box 97)
    - Defense - Armed Services Hospitalization & Health Issues 1971-1972 (Box 97)
    - Defense - Army 1966-1970, 5 folders (Box 97)
    - Defense - Army 1971-1972, 2 folders (Box 98)
    - Defense - Army - Bids 1971-1972 (Box 98)
    - Defense - Army - Chaplains 1969 (Box 98)
    - Defense - Army - Deactivations 1968 & 1971 (Box 98)
    - Defense - Army - Drug Abuse 1970-1971 (Box 98)
    - Defense - Army - The Flag 1970-1971 (Box 98)
    - Defense - Army - Food Service Program 1972 (Box 98)
    - Defense - Army - Fort Eustis Ship Repair Facility 1971 (Box 98)
    - Defense - Army - Fort Lee & Hopewell Sewage Treatment Problems 1969 (Box 98)
    - Defense - Army - Green Berets 1969 (Box 98)
    - Defense - Army - Kennedy (Robert F.) Gravesite 1969-1971 (Box 98)
    - Defense - Army - My Lai Massacre and the Trial of Lt. Calley 1969-1971, 4 folders (Box 98)
    - Defense - Army - Nerve Gas 1970-1971 (Box 98)
    - Defense - Army - Nike Bases 1969 & 1972 (Box 98)
    - Defense - Army - Participation in World Shooting Championships (N.R.A.) 1970 (Box 98)
    - Defense - Army - Presidio Stockade, San Francisco, California 1969 (Box 98)
    - Defense - Army - Radford Arsenal 1969-1972 (Box 98)
    - Defense - Army - Reduction-In-Force 1969-1972 (Box 98)
    - Defense - Army - Re-enlistment 1972 (Box 98)
    - Defense - Army - Relocations 1968-1972 (Box 98)
    - Defense - Army - Relocations - Continental Army Command 1969-1972 (Box 98)
    - Defense - Army - Relocations - General Equipment Testing Activity (GETA) at Fort Lee 1971 (Box 98)
    - Defense - Army - Relocations - Recruiting Stations 1968-1972 (Box 98)
    - Defense - Army - Reorganization of the Third Howitzer Battalion 1967 (Box 98)
    - Defense - Army - Transmitter Site at Woodbridge 1969-1971, 2 folders (Box 98)
    - Defense - Budget and Spending 1971-1972 (Box 98)
    - Defense - Civil Defense 1968 & 1972 (Box 98)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers 1966-1967, 3 folders (Box 98)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers 1968-1972, 17 folders (Box 99)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - Albemarle and Chesapeake Canal Great Bridge 1968-1970 (Box 99)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - Atlantic Coast Deepwater Port Facilities Study 1972 (Box 99)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - Bellwood Depot Easement 1970-1971 (Box 100)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - Chesapeake Bay Hydraulic Model 1969-1972 (Box 100)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - Chincoteague Inlet 1970-1971 (Box 100)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - Coastline Erosion 1970-1972 (Box 100)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - Cranes Nest River 1970 (Box 100)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - Craney Island 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 100)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - Dismal Swamp Canal 1970-1971 (Box 100)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - District Engineers' Move to Baltimore 1970-1971, 2 folders (Box 100)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - Dredging Projects 1969-1971 (Box 100)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - Elizabeth River 1970-1972 (Box 100)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - Elizabeth River - Lambert's Point 1969-1970 (Box 100)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - Florida, Canal Across 1970-1971 (Box 100)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - Four Mile Run Flood Control Project 1969-1972, n.d., 9 folders (Box 100)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - Gathright Dam 1969-1972 (Box 100)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - Goodwin Island/Mobjack Bay Project 1968-1969 (Box 100)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - Hampton Roads 1967 & 1970 (Box 100)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - Intracoastal Waterway 1967-1969 (Box 100)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - James River and the Hipes Dam Project 1967-1972 (Box 101)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - Miscellaneous Projects A- Z 1968-1970 (Box 101)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - Northwest River and the City of Chesapeake 1970-1972 (Box 101)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - Piankatank River/ VEPCO Crossing 1969 (Box 101)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - Potomac River Basin 1967-1970 (Box 101)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - Roanoke River Basin 1970-1971 (Box 101)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - Waynesboro Flood Control Project 1972 (Box 101)
    - Defense - Corps of Engineers - York River Project & the Record of a Public Meeting re Channel Improvements on April 21, 1972 1972, 2 folders (Box 101)
    - Defense - Defense Posture 1970-1972, 2 folders (Box 101)
    - Defense - Defense Supply Agency 1968-1971 (Box 101)
    - Defense - Defoliation in Indochina 1972 (Box 101)
    - Defense - Documentary "Selling of the Pentagon" 1971 (Box 101)
    - Defense - Education 1970-1971 (Box 101)
    - Defense - Janitorial Service 1969-1971 (Box 101)
    - Defense - Langley Research Center 1971 (Box 101)
    - Defense - Marine Corps 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 101)
    - Defense - Merit Promotions 1970-1972, 2 folders (Box 101)
    - Defense - Military Aircraft 1969-1972 (Box 101)
    - Defense - National Cemeteries 1967-1972 (Box 101)
    - Defense - National Guard 1967-1971 (Box 101)
    - Defense - Navy 1967-1969, 4 folders (Box 101)
    - Defense - Navy 1970-1972, 4 folders (Box 102)
    - Defense - Navy - Aircraft Painters 1971 (Box 102)
    - Defense - Navy - Bureau of Naval Personnel Move 1971 (Box 102)
    - Defense - Navy - Cheatham Annex 1970-1972 (Box 102)
    - Defense - Navy - Chesapeake Bay Bridge Tunnel Accident 1970-1972 (Box 102)
    - Defense - Navy - Contract Protest 1969-1970 (Box 102)
    - Defense - Navy - Contracting Out 1968-1972, 2 folders (Box 102)
    - Defense - Navy - Discrimination & Hiring Practices 1971-1972 (Box 102)
    - Defense - Navy - Employment of Military vs Civilians 1971-1972 (Box 102)
    - Defense - Navy - Firefighters 1969 & 1972 (Box 102)
    - Defense - Navy - Hampton Roads Port & Polish Ships, etc. 1972 (Box 102)
    - Defense - Navy - Home Ports n.d. (Box 102)
    - Defense - Navy - Housing 1970-1972 (Box 102)
    - Defense - Navy - Military Post Exchanges 1972 (Box 102)
    - Defense - Navy - Naming of Ship (Robert D. Powers) 1972 (Box 102)
    - Defense - Navy - Naval Air Rework Facility 1969-1972 (Box 102)
    - Defense - Navy - Naval Air Station - Oceana 1969-1972 (Box 102)
    - Defense - Navy - Naval Air Station - St. Helena Property 1966-1970 (Box 102)
    - Defense - Navy - Naval Supply Center - Complaints 1971-1972 (Box 102)
    - Defense - Navy - Naval Supply Center - Locomotive 1972 (Box 102)
    - Defense - Navy - Naval Supply Center - Stevedores 1969-1971, 2 folders (Box 102)
    - Defense - Navy - Naval Weapons Lab, Dahlgren, Virginia n.d. (Box 102)
    - Defense - Navy - Newport News Shipbuilding & Drydock Company 1971-1972 (Box 102)
    - Defense - Navy - Norfolk Naval Shipyard 1967-1970, 3 folders (Box 102)
    - Defense - Navy- Norfolk Naval Shipyard 1971-1972 (Box 103)
    - Defense - Navy - Norfolk Naval Shipyard - Overtime 1970-1971 (Box 103)
    - Defense - Navy - Norfolk Naval Shipyard - Pattern Makers 1967-1971 (Box 103)
    - Defense - Navy - Norfolk Naval Shipyard - Reorganization 1969-1971 (Box 103)
    - Defense - Navy - Norfolk Naval Shipyard -Union Elections 1969-1970 (Box 103)
    - Defense - Navy - Private Shipyards 1971 (Box 103)
    - Defense - Navy - Private Shipyards (Horne Brothers) 1971-1972 (Box 103)
    - Defense - Navy - Reduction-In-Force 1972 (Box 103)
    - Defense - Navy - Relocations of Units 1970-1972 (Box 103)
    - Defense - Navy - Ship Assignments 1970-1972 (Box 103)
    - Defense - Navy - Submarines 1970-1971 (Box 103)
    - Defense - Navy - Survival Equipment Mechanics 1970-1972 (Box 103)
    - Defense - Navy - U.S.S. John F. Kennedy 1972 (Box 103)
    - Defense - Navy - U.S.S. Newport News 1970-1972 (Box 103)
    - Defense - Navy - U.S.S. Virginia 1972 (Box 103)
    - Defense - Navy - VEPCO Powerline, Hybla Valley 1968 (Box 103)
    - Defense - Navy - Wage Board Survey 1970, 4 folders (Box 103)
    - Defense - Navy - Wage Policy 1968-1972 (Box 103)
    - Defense - Navy - Wage Policy - Aeronautical Examiners 1968-1970, 2 folders (Box 103)
    - Defense - Navy - Wage Policy - Government Inspectors 1969-1972 (Box 103)
    - Defense - Navy - Wage Policy - Set-Asides 1968-1972, 3 folders (Box 103)
    - Defense - Navy - Wage Policy - Superintendents & Supervisors 1967-1972, 3 folders (Box 103)
    - Defense - Navy - Wage Policy - Technical Engineers 1968-1970 (Box 103)
    - Defense - Navy - Wage Scales 1969-1972 (Box 104)
    - Defense - Navy - Wallops Island Firing Range 1968-1969 (Box 104)
    - Defense - Navy - Workloads 1969-1972, 4 folders (Box 104)
    - Defense - Newspaper articles re 1970-1971 (Box 104)
    - Defense - Nuclear Weapons 1967-1968 (Box 104)
    - Defense - Optometrists Contracts 1970-1971 (Box 104)
    - Defense - Procurement 1968-1972 (Box 104)
    - Defense - Reconnaissance Plane Shot Down by North Korea 1969 (Box 104)
    - Defense - Regional Subsistence Supply Office Move from Richmond to New York 1969-1970 (Box 104)
    - Defense - Shipment of Possessions at Government Expense 1968 & 1971 (Box 104)
    - Defense - St. Lawrence Seaway 1970 (Box 104)
    - Defense - Temporary Lodging on Military Bases 1970 & 1972 (Box 104)
    - Defense - Vietnam & Cambodia 1967-1972 (Box 104)
    - District of Columbia 1967-1972, 5 folders (Box 104)
    - District of Columbia - W.V. & M. Coach Company 1971-1972 (Box 104)
    - District of Columbia - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority 1969 & 1972 (Box 104)
    - Economic Opportunity, Office of 1967-1971, 5 folders (Box 104)
    - Economic Opportunity, Office of - Community Action Programs 1967-1971, 4 folders (Box 105)
    - Economic Opportunity, Office of - Family Planning 1968-1972 (Box 105)
    - Economic Opportunity, Office of - Headstart Programs 1967-1969 (Box 105)
    - Economic Opportunity, Office of - Health Programs 1967-1972 (Box 105)
    - Economic Opportunity, Office of - Health Programs - Pilot Health Clinic 1970 (Box 105)
    - Economic Opportunity, Office of - Independent Talent Search 1967 (Box 105)
    - Economic Opportunity, Office of - Job Corps 1967-1969 (Box 105)
    - Economic Opportunity, Office of - Legal Services 1967-1969 (Box 105)
    - Economic Opportunity, Office of - Portsmouth Civil Disorders 1970 (Box 105)
    - Economic Opportunity, Office of - Poverty Programs 1969 (Box 105)
    - Economic Opportunity, Office of - Regional Programs A- Z 1967-1971, 2 folders (Box 105)
    - Economic Opportunity, Office of - Spanish Speaking Community 1967-1969 (Box 105)
    - Economic Opportunity, Office of - STOP Program 1968-1972, 2 folders (Box 105)
    - Economic Opportunity, Office of - Upward Bound Programs 1967-1968 (Box 105)
    - Economic Opportunity, Office of - VISTA 1967-1971 (Box 105)
    - Emergency Planning, Office of 1967-1971 (Box 105)
    - Employment 1970-1972 (Box 105)
    - Environmental Protection Agency 1970-1972, 3 folders (Box 105)
    - Environmental Protection Agency - Air Pollution 1971 (Box 105)
    - Environmental Protection Agency - Air Pollution 1972, 2 folders (Box 106)
    - Environmental Protection Agency - News Releases 1971-1972, 3 folders (Box 106)
    - Environmental Protection Agency - Pesticides 1971-1972 (Box 106)
    - Environmental Protection Agency - Solid Wastes 1970-1972, 2 folders (Box 106)
    - Environmental Protection Agency - Water 1970-1972, 2 folders (Box 106)
    - Environmental Protection Agency - Water - Boats 1971 (Box 106)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission 1967-1972 (Box 106)
    - Executive Office of the President 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 106)
    - Executive Office of the President - Conference on Aging 1970-1972 (Box 106)
    - Executive Office of the President - Conference on Children & Youth 1970-1971 (Box 106)
    - Executive Office of the President - Council on Environmental Quality 1970-1972 (Box 106)